# Timothy Josh D.

Experienced Customer Service Specialist with a demonstrated history of working in the internet industry. Skilled in Customer Service, Web Browsing, Public Speaking, Management, and Debate. Strong support professional graduated from North South University.

Email: <u>timjosh94@yahoo.com</u>

Mobile: 01620707005

LinkedIN- https://www.linkedin.com/in/josh-timothy-450153118

Dhaka, Bangladesh

#### **Profile**

I was working as a full-time operations executive at Backpack. My responsibilities in the role included providing customers face to face and over the phone support about their purchase requests. This position has given me key employability skills while also allowing me to experience working in a professional fast-paced startup environment. Even in a very short period of time, I could show my "Go-getter" mentality and play an important role in the organization's daily operations.

# **Experience**

Customer Support Executive and Payment Analyst Backpack Technologies, Dhaka Bangladesh January 2019 - June 2020

- Handle customer issues
- Managing Purchasing and Missing items
- Refunding and Rerouting items
- Handling meetings with high profile clients
- Call support
- Scanning and approving payments
- Fraud detection (International payments)

## **Relations Executive**

SkyTech Ltd, Dhaka Bangladesh

2014-2015

- Handle client queries
- Face-to-face discussions and consultations with clients. Handling Sales Calls

#### **Projects**

**Translator** 

**NGO - Ashirbad** (2012-2014)

- Interpret day long seminars and trainings from Bengali to English
- Visit program sites with donors and help them communicate

## **Volunteering**

**Data Collector** 

Help Age India, Darjeeling, India (2012)

• Conduct surveys and collect data for analysis.

### **Education**

#### **Bachelor of Business Administration (BBA)**

**International Business and Marketing** 

North South University (2014-2019)

CGPA 3.27

**Indian Secondary Certificate (ISC)** 

**Business** 

**Business** 

Mount Hermon School (2012- 2014)

**Indian Certificate of Secondary Education (ISCE)** 

Mount Hermon School (2010- 2012)

Languages

English Expert Bengali Advanced

**Awards** 

**Prefect** High School (2013)

My role was to maintain an atmosphere of friendly cooperation, peace, discipline and unity in the School

**Skills** 

Google Tools Usage of Slack Dropbox Usage Trello

(Docs, Sheets) (Work Communication tool) (Paperdoc etc) (Management Tool)

# References

Lt Col Md. Moazzem Hossain, psc, G (Retd)

M. Sc (Technical), M.D.S (NU) Vice President, HR & Admin Mobile: +8801711408480

Email: moazzem.h@squaregroup.com

**Mr Asif Chowdhury** 

Lecturer & Assistant Proctor M. Sc. In Business Economics & Finance University of Surrey UK BS in Economics (Minor in Finance)

North South University

Phone: +880-2-55668200

Email: asif.chowdhury@northsouth.edu